the silence think it's empty space think a quiet life means a fragile place no crowd around
no noise no show so they assume there's nowhere else to go they lean back start cutting corners
slow fights no scenes no warning signs just a shift you missed between the lines was measuring
the price you pay was just a feel woke up from these midnight like saints with eye foam that
You're pretty good at that.
Flash it like a sweet four-bit and him's like he dreams though.
Hey, hey, hey, what's up guys?
You poised a big, oh, the new catries.
Yeah, well enjoy your night, thank you for coming.
I'm having like a masquerade ball right now.
I'm just pulling in some cards.
Oh shit, well this is my villain's deck
and people were like, oh villain's deck,
but it's actually a really good deck.
Of course, you know, it is a Disney deck, but hey.
You know, Disney's pretty cool.
Okay, ooh, truth, okay.
And I'm just doing a little pyramid spread
and I'll read it and it's like a, ooh, okay.
And let me, I'm gonna get three, three, three.
Hold on, I'm gonna do, ooh, okay.
Okay, okay.
One more, okay.
Interesting.
Okay, yeah, go to the community post.
Do I see the title of the live stream?
Oh yeah, I did see the, I saw the title,
but you know, it's like,
It goes deeper than, and now it's getting to legal things.
I mean, I think I'm about to be sued because, let me see,
what do I do?
I played my music too loud or something,
and my neighbor got upset because he couldn't sleep
at 9.30 PM at night because of B2Screaming on my TV.
Okay, well, anyway, okay.
Well, we start with this little snake, a little snakey.
The dog bark, you know, that's a neighbor's dog.
That's a neighbor's dog, but, you know,
they do say when there's a dog barking,
like, heck-a-tay is there,
and I guess that's a good sign for this reading.
Also, I would say confirmations, you know,
and make some sort of noises,
made motorcycles and stuff like that during a reading.
There you go.
So we have this snake, and he's kind of like, you know,
he's all full of himself, okay?
And this is the, okay, so this is the two of coins,
and it's like, you know.
Um, I would say this is somebody imbalanced. This is a snake. They have this other like agenda, and it's like, you know
What if they say about snakes? It's always like
Beyond any huge huge thing. There's always a head of a snake, right? It's like the head vampire or something
And so it starts with this such as this little like, you know, don't know if the snake came out of there or whatever, but
Okay, we have the three of wands this looks like Ursula's cauldron is bubbling and I think that you know
Maybe a couple goes those coins got thrown in there. Maybe or maybe there's three people there doing some kind of third-party
Buckery, okay, it can be more than three people. It could be a whole gang of people about you know, okay, sweetie
You have a slithery little sneaky snake
Oh, you are a ghosty. Yeah, have you heard of the ghost project ghost?
Hey, there's also a magician, but this is more of a voodoo magician.
So this is somebody that's able to deal with some of these energies.
I don't know if he's over the cauldron.
During that himself, but there is some kind of like practitioner.
Let me see what it looks like. Oh, he's doing these shadowy things with his hands.
It's voodoo. It looks like, what is it, like Baron Samadhi.
I haven't seen this movie, but he's got a little voodoo doll.
He's got tarot cards, and there's shadows projected.
And so there's some illusion going on too.
Okay, that's the first row.
Neither the second row.
King of Cups with Captain Hook.
Okay, just like trying to hook somebody in.
I mean, it's like, the Cups is usually like,
somebody would really control their emotions,
but he was just a very emotional man.
But,
You know, he's also held it on its kind of revenge and something like that and trying to like catch
Somebody for something and it's kind of appropriate. We have a crab and the Sun right there
okay, so
Maybe there's something that's being illuminated at the same time
I see for this whoever this king is that's like trying to like
He's looking at maps. He's trying to like figure something out, right?
And so he doesn't see the, this behind the sun, he doesn't see it, it's like, he doesn't see a
clips or something like that. And it's behind him, right? So maybe there's some kind of shadows,
some kind of, also this in the middle, it's a crossroads of the whole thing. Having the sun
as a crossroads is kind of like interesting. I'm getting like a big, bringing something into the
world vibe. Again, and I get it still with this, we have a, we have seven, sorry, this, we have this
eight of wands.
I'm sorry, it's the Seven of Wands, okay?
Sorry.
The Seven of Wands, it looks like there's some kind of like
path, path is revealed itself, okay?
You have to kind of watch out,
because you can see what at the end of the path.
There's a little cottage,
but there's like, it's being watched over
by this wicked queen, okay?
And so, yeah, seven.
I mean, the seven is also like, you know,
kind of almost reminds me of like a path to like,
You know seven is a number of sacrifice usually, but we also have this one's queen of coins. This is a greedy
Well, I mean it's this is
There were villainous in this but look at the snake at her feet. Is that a snake? What is that thing?
Turtle?
She's writing. I never seen this movie either. I suppose it's called the uh, not sure what it's called
I haven't seen this movie, but
You can just tell she's like wanting to fill that little treasure chest
And what do we have?
We have this Eight of Swords.
Eight of Swords, they're gonna end up trapped
in their own mines, okay?
There's so much they don't see.
There's so much they don't see,
because it's like, I think something's catching up.
Something about to catch up and they won't be able to,
they're gonna need to either,
let me look at the card carefully.
Is that the Lion King?
Where's my glasses?
Can I wear glasses with these glasses?
I don't want to wear my glasses.
I don't know. I don't see him. Okay
Okay, okay. Yeah, it is the lion. It's the lion king. He's it's a I think it's garbage. He's cornered
So this is got someone's gonna get caught, you know
But there's a lot of people right there, right?
So it's like I think they've done something to a lot of people. It's caught up with them. It looks like they're the hyenas
Going after this old lion
He's like what what I do
Yeah, what's up? Yeah, you like the tarot card. They're cool. They're really cool cards
And then I have a deck this is called the haters expose deck and I know all of us they're dealing with these haters
I almost have the crystal and eyes a little bit doesn't it looks like crystal and eyes
You know crystal and was saying she might she's thinking of just to spite everybody. She's gonna drop Sam and strikes
That's up to her, but it's kind of funny that
You know, I guess she she was looking for you know,
245 to like, you know, hold hold her hand and stuff like that
During I guess he's having a crisis. I hope if it's true. I mean, I hope that she is known for making a stuff up a little bit
But yeah, it looks like this is not like a crystal and yeah
little little
Wow
I like the blowfish that Kate did with her. I mean, it's like, you know, so there's competition. Okay
So somebody considers you competition or you are like the real competition is always trying to one-up you you have someone like that around
Okay, someone's looking in the rear view. They're like not looking at the road. They're looking at the person like
Behind them and they're like, I gotta be ahead. I gotta be ahead. I gotta be ahead. We're watching. Okay
Oh, we have
Their own worst enemy. Okay
They cause most of their own problems, most of the bad things that happen are caused by themselves.
Yeah, the cape did a blowfish of her. Yeah, it might have been inspired by, you know, I did have a...
I had a blowfish up, but who did I say it was? Well, a few people.
It's SIG. SIG. Yeah. Oh, we have toxic. This looks like crystalline, too.
It's crystalline right there. No, it's just too skinny. Okay. It says...
be careful not to indulge in
you know
Toxic substances, okay?
Because it looks like there's like but it looks like kind of like there's like people putting them on this person, right?
It's like so yeah, it's like maybe like that's a that's a thing against like peer pressure because maybe there's some people that want to
Get you inevrated or out of your mind or like looking like that. Okay. Hold on. It's okay. Oh, you got lowest out the steam
Okay, well, I hope everyone you know here has like a good self-esteem
But I do think that your attacker has some low self-esteem and these insecurity issues
or something, because it says their envy and inferiority attitude towards you stems from
their own deep childhood wounds, okay?
Let's do three more.
Scorned love.
Maybe this person had a crush on you or something, or there's something that they liked.
Pains of rejection and betrayal. Okay, maybe somebody's out to get you x to grind because they feel betrayed or because they feel scorn
And they wanted you they have you so nobody else will or something. I've got I'm gonna think might
I will not be ignored Alex. That's from a fatal attraction. There's a tiger's eye
Tiger's Eye. So that's a stone. It helps with the grounding, protection, self-confidence, inner strength, willpower, and clarity.
You might want to go, who's having a crisis? There's a lot of people having a crisis right now.
There's a lot of things. Whatever applies, take it. This will be messages for somebody or confirmation.
Just take what resonates, I would say.
This one says, keep a protection pouch with you. I would say, you know, because there's stuff you can't see happening.
There's because a lot of stuff happens behind the scenes, right?
And so there's having this supernatural protection. I would say put it for the obsidian put a put a tiger's eye in it put a
Lucky charm it brought rabbits, but I don't know whatever you have a little if the company gree gree bags
You know these little bags of because this person's a copycat
They're trying to be everything that you are do everything they're trying to copy everything you do
It could be in a mocking way, but could be like they actually like your style, right? You're having a crisis Nancy. I'm sorry
There's a earth sign that is causing you negativity. Okay, there's a person causing you negative. They're an earth sign
Good times has the same green screen set up as me. Well, yeah, but he doesn't really use I mean
I should use it
But it's like you can't see my cards as well when I have it on so I'm gonna have it off for a minute and
Finally personality disorder. They don't know how to be themselves
So sometimes they do people have deep-seated emotional issues, but here's what the sad things
I'll go over a little bit, you know hurt people hurt people like for example
You know there's I had this bully and I was you know, I blame the bully for a lot of things
And I've learned some more things about the bully today that makes me think
my
Yeah
The credit is always given and it's like it's always thought is there is there more behind this bully than just
Oh here hurt people hurt people
Yo
Yo, what's up?
How are you?
I'm doing a good site. I see you're back on your main channel. I am there we go
Don't look at it. They're right. We're in the right place now
And I have four eyes now see it in that this is a cover my bald my huge bald spot
I have in the front of my head, so you can't even see it right now, but uh
Yeah, you know you shave. I just in the mustache. So
He's gone. Oh, I got a I got a haircut. Did you see? Oh, it looks good
Oh, no, now I'm gonna get so much shit. Oh, he looks like he's a teenager. Oh my god
You're so they're gonna call me perverted and stuff cuz they're gonna say well at least they're not gonna say you look like an embryo
But yeah, my bald spot. I know like, you know, everyone's saying oh, I need Rogan press like look at how bad it look
Horrible it is any pair clip for men. I'm not just a member. I'm in the president, but uh, yeah
Anyway, you know, definitely the good ball my favorite bodybuilder on YouTube is hot
But he's fucking like picks up his hat or his little like
There's little like a what's a ski hat and he's completely bald and he's like 30
He looks good. Yeah
Richard hat. What's up to all these viewers? I just into my stream
I sent your link out so maybe some go hi everybody that came good times life is the same green screen
Yeah, oh, you know who came today was like one of your people. I met in your chat. They're really cool. Yeah, the vulga
Oh vulga. Yeah, I told vulga. It's my moderator. I told vulgar to watch your stream. Yeah
Thank you.
That was really cool.
I thought you were funny when you went on to my show and you started dancing your speedo
and forced to chill out.
I'm glad people like that.
You know, it's like, and I'll put myself through these ridiculous things and do it,
but it's like, I know there are some people out there that like to like get people to
do it and then take credit.
But I see, I saw something today that was just so disturbing.
I looked at Good Time Sun.
Oh my gosh.
Wow.
He does look like he could be with my father. I think I might be older than him
Maybe just really think he's maybe you're older than me or something like that
But yeah, I mean I saw I saw things today. I saw people drinking from toilets. I saw people smearing manure into their face
I saw I saw people in a bunch of desperate desperate situations, and I was like, well, why are they doing that?
I see I wouldn't do it. Wow. Is that some macaroni and cheese?
Lasagna. Oh, it looks good. It's good. Yeah, and going up its heat
Hey in the moon, it's Sarah. Let me see who's this person backstage? Let me see
I might have to put I'm gonna put the thing up for a second about the screen up and I'm gonna bring up a guest
This is someone that wants to say hello. So
Let's welcome to the show. Yeah
Jared
Jared you're a nigger. Oh shut up. I
Do not endorse that horrible language that the person was just here to demonstrate
ignorance
But uh, and so never be like that person guys never be like that person would say such a word. I'm terrible
What a disgusting person, but anyway, they're just trolls
They're just trolls. I know but you know what on YouTube if you actually like, you know
You can say that word, but then you have to say
Don't use that word or something like that and then it all evens out. So I know the trick. So, uh
So, yeah, it's under like a
That sounded like sick
Maybe I don't know his name is James Jorgensen or something. I forgot what his name was, but Jared Jorgensen on Jared
This is the subway guy. I'm not sure but anyway, he can't call him. I should have been put five bucks on it
Did that was sick? Okay
The way he said it it just sounded like you know how sick has that under bite. Yeah
His mouth looks really weird now. I thought he I thought he broke his jaw or something his teeth are
It looks like really weird. I don't know.
Yeah, but he's not he's like actually nice, but you know small quantities
But anyway, yeah, you got 50 viewers psych you're famous. Whoa
What's the show?
It's a warm need to
Start taking off my clothes. I'm just gonna how about I did how about I do something like you know
I start dress getting in women's clothes and stuff that'd be fun and putting on lipstick and smearing on my face like Courtney
Love that'd be a cool thing to do that'd be
But then I would foil it, the person wanting to me to do that, you know, for them and then
embarrass myself.
I've already embarrassed myself so much that it's like I really can't get any more embarrassed
than I've already been.
So it's kind of like broke the embarrassment clock.
So I'm pretty lucky.
Have you seen Paige has been going live a lot, Paige?
She's doing great.
Yeah, it looks great.
I mean, she's doing great.
And I know she gets a lot of trolls too.
That she she's good at dealing with they go in her chat and they say that she's doing demonic satanic rituals
Well, fuck them. I mean, it's like, you know, she's said she's a proud, you know
practitioner of wicca or
You know, but after whatever I don't know. She's a good witch though. She's not a bad witch like beta
Or even if beta is not a witch. She looks like the wicked witch of the West, you know, so
Hey, just like Linda. There's a difference. Okay. There's good witches and bad witches
And good witches are good looking and bad witches are ugly. We all know that right so psych
So you have like you haven't streamed for a while. It's just like one of your first streams back a few days
Yeah, so
What is up with like the way that you're?
Your your streams are like I noticed like a lot of people lurk in your chat like yeah
A lot of people do I might be gangstalked by somebody. Oh, we have a joke. We have a guest here. Hello
You're still a nigger. Oh, no
Karen, I can't believe you would do that. That didn't sound like sick. It wasn't sick
I know I think that wasn't that wasn't Karen. It said it said grateful on this day. It's not her. Thank God
I could have a form long
I should write a book about my experience.
I don't understand.
Yeah, I will.
Guys, I have the codex.
It's like translated everything.
That was sick.
It was sick.
Dancing thinks it was sick too.
I know, wasn't you?
I was just, I was just kidding.
I was just kidding.
It said, it said, grateful.
And I had your picture.
I mean, but people are so weird.
But you know what?
He said, I was vinegar.
and he was oil, and he wants to mix up with me
and get on a salad, I don't know.
Hey, yeah, that's a good idea, I'm gonna write a book,
you know, and it's gonna be even bigger,
better than the Trollopedia.
There's this guy that joined my stream,
and his name was like, Chobot,
and he's like, he looks like Groove from Despicable Me.
He joined my podcast yesterday and today,
and anyways, getting to it's like,
he's writing a memoir, and he literally
is definitely on the spectrum.
So anybody can write a memoir now it is sure or because you can self-publish very easily you can do print on demand
I mean, it's like it's not like you know
You have to go to a publishing house and get approved and get paid to do a book you can make anything right it makes a
Duplicates, yeah make a duplicate sick account. His name is what's his name? It's like a Larry Nash or something like that
But um, yeah
Um, so yeah, he wasn't that smart. I mean, it's like, you know, you who else came today was like that fifth sage
He came up and started calling me n-word f-a-g-o-t and I kept bringing him back up. I'm so dumb
Did he sign it? So he kept a stroke. It looks like he did. He looked like
And then he's like looking up at the camera like
And I like he looks like a blowfish, I don't know. He looks he looks he's
Crystal and would produce beautiful blowfish children like thing
Yeah. Why are there cheeks like that? There are cheeks like circles.
I don't know, but you see, if you've found Crystal Anne on this deck, there's her eyes
right there, see? Yeah. You know Crystal Anne on it.
That is her eyes. That is her eyes. And then she kind of looks like the one at the top
of this deck, too.
Yeah
Yeah, so stick a stick a screw, but um
Hey Rudy, how are you? So how is your week going? It's Wednesday. I can't believe the week is going so fast
Today I went to the hair salon and got a haircut at my hair appointment
So one of my friends said that it was gay that I got they said are you gay you went to a salon to get your hair cut
That's not gay. I mean it's like
Well, did you go into one of those masculine barber shops like, you know, or is like, well, it's a half barber shop, half salon.
Okay. So there was the men on one side, the women on the other.
Well, I got my haircut by a woman.
Okay, good.
And had a very gentle touch.
Wonderful.
Like, did you rub your, rub your neck a little bit? I had, I went to this biker kind of like Mexican kind of like 50s style place and then I got a shave.
Who looks like Blackout Andy?
I'm not even close to Blackout Andy.
Blackout Andy looks like, I don't know,
he looks like some celebrity.
I don't know if it's like the,
he has a look, definitely.
He just says I have a voice for Hollywood,
but unless he, he does Elmer Fudd, you know, but.
Blackout Andy looks like Ursula.
More, you think about it.
He certainly has a big puss, but.
Oh, he got arrested twice.
I saw him, he was in, I think bloggers,
I saw a video blogger today, I saw his penis.
in the video, I've seen him butthole before too.
He had a freak off light last year
and I saw a couple quotes from me.
He got leaked.
It was impressive.
Ha ha ha, wasn't it impressive?
His butthole looks like it's blowing a balloon
for some reason, I don't know.
There's some kind of weird growth,
like someone's in a prolapse.
I don't even know if,
it looks like it's inside out a little bit.
Or someone needs to blow it out.
Why would he show his butthole?
Why would he show his butt?
Khabita.
Why are you wearing broken headphones? These are my old headphones. I got new headphones. These are beats. I have new headphones
If I can find them, but I just like to wear these beats because it beats
But it's not even fitting on here
Yeah, they're they're broken dude. They're broke. Oh
That's duct tape gets inducted. It's hanging on by a thread. Oh
Those are in beats. So they're nice. Yeah, I like beats
so
Be you know what Michael Jackson's favorite better headphones was they were called the beat it's
I guess I can switch it to this side. So you can't yeah, you look like a receptionist from the
You look like a male phone sex operator actually
Hello
This is a professional podcast studio psych. We have a broken apart. I forgot I forgot I forgot I'm so unprofessional
I don't know somebody got a haircut. I know look at Nancy noticed but
My hair is just pulled back, but I want I'm gonna copy. I'm gonna get the same kind of hairstyle as Joker and I'm gonna
I'm gonna try to be his his tall skinny twin
You know, I'm just kidding. How about what if I started wearing Joker makeup though? That'd be cool
You have 60 viewers site Wow
If I get a hundred viewers
Fuck it, I'll pull up the speedo from the washing machine.
Here's what I like.
There's a person on the show.
I'm totally my idea.
I wasn't worse than to him.
Do you guys think he'll get 100 viewers chat?
What do you guys think the chances are?
Anything is possible.
I cardboard to it, then tape it.
That's what Wiga Studio says.
Okay.
Well, I think it works fine for him.
I like it.
So you're having like a good,
good.
Is Brandon Q still mad at you or mad at us?
Yeah.
Well, remember that Rose person?
That is actually him like trying to get modded and stuff.
So then he can accuse you of having
like a 12 year old as a mod and stuff.
That's what he that's what he's his plan was kind of similar to what gamble tried to do to Aaron Carter with like
But it's just like such a lame way didn't work. Okay, so hi, Paula. How are you doing dude? And
Yeah, and so
Basically, he's all such such weird shit and talks about disgusting things that he's dogging. So I can't deal with it anymore
So he's off
He's banned, and I don't have to worry about it anymore.
But he keeps coming over under names.
He goes, oh, I cut you off.
I made your show.
It's like he made my show.
Ever since he had still showed up,
it never has been like slower, but okay, he made the show.
He also has bots.
He just hires these robots to follow him around.
And then he has them like say to echo
in whatever his like wants to say.
And they'll start, all these bots will come saying,
oh, you have a child mod.
No, it's like so stupid.
Like no. Oh, we have a guest. Let's welcome all the way from beautiful
Canbury, Australia? Let me see
Nice try Jared
Nice try
band
That wasn't that was Liz. I was Jared again. Good thing you you put your background out
Well, yeah, I didn't bring him up because I could see I could see his name. It was the get I mean
I said Jared that was the guy that came up here and called me the n-word. You have 110 viewers. Oh my god. Oh my god
We have to pull out your speedo. Oh my god. I do. Oh my god. Well, I'll get a hundred. I need to finish my bureau
I'll get into it. Hey, I had such a good time in my speedo
I look good in a speedo, but you know, I was told by someone said today
I look like I'm a maceater and I need like, you know to go to a second
A-N-O-R-E-X-I-A clinic or something like that.
I've been to Skinny's since I was like 18.
And so that's Jared, not sick.
Yeah, I mean, it's like they use the name,
but that's, yeah, it's someone named Jared,
but I don't know if it's the same.
Oh, Speedotime, okay.
Let me see if the, are they clean?
Yeah, they're clean.
I'll get them out of the thing in a bit.
Yeah, chat loves it.
Oh my God.
Well, I wear it well. Thank you. Well, you know, it came with this big piece of foam in the crotch
And I just like I was like, you know fuck it
I mean, I'm secure enough without this huge piece of foam and it still looks pretty decent. I
Mean not as big. I mean, it's like I would love that foam. It's just like, you know, it's a little bit too much
You know, you're like our chippin deals porn star for doing a front flip in the speedo on your bed
On my bed a front flip on my bed. I don't know how to do a flip though. I've done it
I did a headstand once but
Okay, let me go. Oh, yeah, that's what he asked. Okay. Well, we get I'll try to do that
But I'll do a headstand for like a donation, but I'm not gonna
Speedo time chat
W chat, bro. What do you guys think he's gonna be wearing speedo the Joker could drink. Yeah, I don't drink dude
I don't drink. I got a haircut. My name is kangarooski
I bet, I bet Beto's jealous right now, Psych.
What'd you say?
I bet Beto's jealous.
Oh my god.
She had my legs and my beautiful shaved bush.
Yeah, we're ready.
We're getting ready to help you.
You guys can't see me, right?
Thank god.
Okay, perfect.
Okay, are you ready, guys?
Here I come.
I'm getting my mask too.
So much fun.
Okay.
Well, I'm in my blue source.
I need to like,
yeah, I'm gonna work,
I'm gonna work into it here.
So I'll start unbuttoning Wow the Joker quit drinking. He didn't quit drinking. I think it's uh, it's like
Okay, you ever see my new tattoo Joe. Oh, you saw how I fixed my tattoo. Did you ever see that? Yeah?
Okay, hey, I want to show you these things that they're called the Horus wands. Oh, it's called the wands of Horus
And this is like special spiritual technology.
You get these two rods right there.
I think they're copper or something.
Have a little shake to it.
You meditate by holding like this.
These are supposedly some kind of ancient Egyptian technology
that help with meditation.
That's pretty good.
Get an Uncle Sam hat.
Okay.
I mean, I need Uncle Sam hat.
Can someone please donate an Uncle Sam hat?
Cause it is still July.
And so I'm going to do my,
I'm going to get my mood lighting on and then we're right.
Hold on.
Okay, I'm gonna tie something around myself.
Okay, this thing is so sexy.
You're gonna love this, okay.
To go with the speedo?
Yeah.
Any Uncle Sam hat?
Can you send me one, please?
Okay, this is my thong.
No, I don't know.
Wow.
What do you think, Gojoker?
Remember, Gojoker, when you went to
Roadback Mountain that year
and you taught me about what the pussy is?
That was psych when he was podcast number one,
drama number one streamer,
and then it drove him crazy.
I didn't know my flexing motor paw, though.
Hold on. Oh, my God.
I feel like a Sumo wrestler.
Okay, come on.
Now he's back.
Joker only likes women?
I'm, like, kind of feminine.
Like, oh, you can imagine, like, if without a wig.
Put a wig on, Saig.
A wig?
No, I had a really cool, like, blonde wig,
but I dropped it in cat food and put it in the washer
and it turned into Medusa's hair,
and so I had to throw it away.
But I can actually put a t-shirt over my head.
It kind of does a good illusion for them.
I'll actually put my shirt,
I'll put my shorts over my head.
Okay, hold on a second, let me just.
Make a jailbreak.
Okay.
I'm just gonna put my shorts over my hair,
but I'm not gonna, hold on, excuse me.
Okay, okay.
So I have blue hair.
Just imagine that this hair is real.
I just wrapped up my little blankie.
Please hit that like button, guys.
I need to do it.
Unwrap me like a present, Joker, under the Christmas tree.
All right, ready?
You want me to unwrap you?
Oh my god, Joker!
Shiee, well that's pretty good.
I like it, now I feel like a mummy.
A sexy fucking mummy.
Okay, well, you know, Joker, just for you,
I'm gonna give you a little special treat.
Okay, oh my god.
I can't really twerk, I know I can twerk better, I mean I'm white, I don't have a butt, yeah, Lord have mercy, oh my god, how embarrassing, oh my god, I look cool like this huh, it pulls out less hair, yeah.
What do you think Joker?
Somebody, they're talking about Jimnick in the chat, what happened to Jimnick?
I think she died, no she's back, no she's around, I think she's around and she's back, but she is, oh she died, oh no, she did, okay, she died.
She got a new liver. Oh, wow. Okay, that's a crazy story. I'm sorry. Yeah, that's cool. That's cool
Hey, you know what you know what you know what you can do with a liver
liver transplant Wow
I'm just a trans
That's living but oh
We have a guest. Let's walk. Oh my god. And now we're in trouble Joker. Hold on. Where was it the right person?
Yes
Let's welcome all the way from beautiful Switzerland, Europe, the gorgeous, beautiful, and inspiring
James Bond!
Hello my sweetheart!
Hi!
Oh hi darling!
How are you?
We're doing a white chocolate Oreo.
I was like, white on the outside and then...
Oh my goodness on the inside.
Dang!
How are you?
Oh, great! What are you doing, my beautiful? What are you doing?
I'm good. I'm celebrating the 4th of July.
Wow! Oh my goodness, you look gorgeous.
Thank you.
What?
I have confidence to give you. It's like, you know, I have confidence.
I don't care if I, you know, I look like I'm one of the people, you know, pushing the oven in Germany. I don't care.
Are you still celebrating, wait, wait, wait, are you still celebrating the 4th of July?
I celebrate it from the middle of June until the end of December, right?
Doesn't sound Swiss, yeah.
Your eyes, yeah.
You can't take your eyes off me, can you?
Hey, there's White Dog, hello.
Oh, God.
I think I look good I would totally do myself if I like you know met myself
something is your guest who is your handsome friend mr. Extendo say hi to
mr. Extendo mix mix mix stand oh hello mix stand how you doing sir you can
just call me tender on 10 do it's like it's like Nintendo
I am the real 007 James Bond.
Okay, so many of these counterfeit 007 people around here. I'm like, what the fuck are all these 007 people doing?
None of them are James Bond. This is the real James Bond. She's fucking better than any of them.
The real 007 James Bond. Hello to everybody.
You know what? They call me Octopussy.
How you doing? It's been a while, I was like, you know who?
Yes, how are you doing? Okay, you know, you know that Alexander McQueen we you know
He was such a nice person, but he's totally turned against me and
What has he done again, what has he been up to let's just say
He's doing very bad things and he's being very rude and he's banned from the show
Can not come up because Empress Chinchilla is a porn bomber, but she can sit in the chat watch. She's friends with
No, he palm bombs and he it seems like that is very common with him because everywhere he goes
I keep hearing he's been porn bombing people and he takes pride in doing that too. He actually
I've heard him say I love porn bombing. I'm gonna do it and I'll do it again. Oh my god.
Yeah, but he doesn't even porn bomb with his own dick. He porn bombs with some like, you know,
black guy's cock and then he like even does this to his friends and then no one wants to hang out
with them anymore because he's so annoying.
I mean, I do like a good black cock, but not like, you know on my show. Oh, yeah, like a fake shit
I mean that would I mean if he's gonna do it. I mean do it with your own dick
Right, I mean Aldi when Aldi for dick. Come on Alex
Magina even 300 low, I think I saw the balls before I don't think I've seen jokers balls
But I have seen them in boxers twerking and doing push-ups and stuff
There's more time in a really
Well, you are actually the only one that I've seen expose yourself in your shots and and in your your your American flag
I've never seen anybody
I'm old to be American I'm proud of you guys look at my abs look at those abs you see like abs
like that every day look how like beautiful I am yeah I just love myself oh my god oh that is
you see my alien you are you are sexy you are sexy there's my alien right here hold on where's the
alien there you go
You're gonna see her over there. You're sexy. You're sexy. What do you think Nintendo? What do you think?
I think that psych needs to be more aerobatic acrobatic. Okay, I'm gonna try to do a car wheel.
I'll do it. I'm gonna do a toe touch. How about that?
I need once more
Wow
Many push-ups can you do inside?
I couldn't even do that shit. I couldn't even
10.
11.
That's good.
You could have given 10.
You could have given, oh.
I tried my best.
I got winded.
I haven't done those.
I haven't done exercise in a long time.
Hold on.
I need to click.
3, 2, 1, go.
Yeah, I think I'm thinking of just doing it just I'm gonna quit last year be I'm just gonna do I'm just gonna do speedo push-up streams
I'm gonna see how that goes for me
Amazing you did you did in I couldn't I think I could have done two push-ups and I would be over
How many can you do Joker?
Or Kendo
Uh, like 10. Okay
Well, I mean
Joker and I used to have a lot of fun like he'd like you know
He used to they pull up his shirt and he draw like like a mouth on his belly button and like little circle on his nipples
And it looked like he had a character in that noble Castro. Oh, it's noble. Hey, what's up, dude?
I'll make you a mind
No, I have a hundred forty-seven
Mexican one next time. I'm so sorry
Mexican Mexican
Okay
He's actually a musician and stuff. I'll make him. He's like, yeah facts. What's up? Okay. Good. There he goes flex
Actually, I met some guy today. I won't say who he was but he was like, hey, what do you think psyche?
He flexed and I was like whoa
And I feel like fucking
Who you know how are you swimming in naked form? But who else guy like got a lot of like women naked for them?
You have to know I guess I don't know
Okay
I'm a little bit winded, but now I'm all getting swayed.
Wow, so James, what's been going on?
Are you there?
Oh, here you take you.
James?
Here's a card.
Give me some kind of.
Give a little echo?
I don't know.
I was gonna pull a few cards for you.
Okay, we got the page of sorts. This is like somebody's buying or somebody's watching over something
There's a little there's a little curious cat. I think it's a cat from somewhere
There's some kind of intercom coming in. I don't know what it is. It's not
Yeah
There's one small superman, one giant superman kind.
How do they have a telephone on the moon?
I don't understand, I mean, it's like a cell phone.
I mean, I had a great reception.
It has better reception than my cell phone,
like right in the local areas.
How do they do that?
NASA is just amazing.
I am out of breath.
But you did get this tiger right there, the emperor.
It's like beautiful.
Masculine
Authoritative energy you're about oh, you're about to be when you drop this music. Okay. Hold on. It's like I'm gonna make you a mod
So I'll share I'll share it if I can't he's really good. He's like really talented
Yeah, so how's Switzerland? What time is it over there right now?
New Suisse. Are you a Swiss miss? Oh?
I think we lost her but here. I'm gonna there you go. You got a mod
Drop your song if you want. I'll play it. Okay
Yeah, I mean really but I'm really proud of you Joker you're doing really well on your show
And it's like I'm glad you've been built it back up, you know, you know what to do you're about yeah your um your chat loves you
I mean it's like the chat and it's kind of funny because
You know, it's like kind of friendlier trolls. They're not like
Yes, yes
There was some kind of interaction taking place.
What was that?
Maybe like some kind of spy agency
is interfering with your phone, but it's hope not.
So I forgot what I forgot, but how is there somebody like there's someone that keeps coming in my chat
I was wondering if it's you. No, I haven't won call me a cute white boy
That's what they you're cute. Oh, I would I would say that but I would say you're a cute white man
Cute white boy you are a cute white boy
Guess guess his age if you just saw him walking on the street, what age would you think he would be?
Um, let me guess, let me see, wait a minute, wait a minute, um, he, um, wait a minute,
he's, he's, he's, he's got a, listen, I'm seeing like a white face.
I'm not seeing, does he have a, let me just ask, oh, okay, now he's turned, oh, oh my
goodness, he's, oh my goodness, he's, oh, Jesus Christ, he's cute as an angel.
I know, you should see, you should see him with his, um, civil war costume on, I love
He was an angel. Oh my goodness. Okay. Oh, you know, I went to Brokeback Mountain one year with them
It was the best year of my life
So I'm gonna guess I'm gonna guess he's
Let he's okay. Let me guess. Let me guess and it's just a guess
he's not pops 30 and
he's gonna be in
middle 20s
You got it exactly
I'm going to give a number because it's quite it's kind of difficult because it's so cute
Not past 30 he's on there. Yeah, it's 26. Yeah. Am I correct Nintendo? Yeah. Yeah, I'm 26
All right. Okay, cool. I got it. Wow. It's confirmed. It's confirmed psych. How do I look James?
How do I look to you?
Well, to you, that's going to be very difficult because you age and you various, it depends
on your moods and your mood swings.
You age and because you carry such a heavy load and you've got such, and when I say
I'm not being serious now. Yeah, don't even give me that smile. Don't why you think I'm calling you?
Why you think I'm calling you?
Good, all right
Now you have me blushing, now you have me blushing, watching straight up your dick.
Okay, so I'm gonna say, I'm gonna say, you are not past 50.
God dang I guys I used to like pass for like in my 30s now. I look 50. Wow make it stop never
45 years old and I look five years
That to me you two I don't have a gray hair, but you to me beat me made my beard all white
And I know oh my gosh, not being accused of stalking Vita and like you know bothering Vita and bring her to tears
Okay, if you saw me would you say how old I am if you saw me?
I would say black don't crack so you look probably, you know
much younger than
I don't know because you have the wisdom in your eye
You've seen me before yeah
Yeah, I would say maybe 40
46 47
Okay, that's a good, that's a good point. I'm fifty seven. Oh, there you go. Great. See
Well, you're beautiful. I love your hair and
I think we've had some great spiritual conversations and like, you know, you've helped me out when I've had low points and stuff and been
pretty free and positive and how amazing is that to have good people in your life?
Especially when you have some bad people, like I've had these really bad trolls. They're not even like
just trolls, they're like people that like try to like ruin your life and like, you know, like, you know, do all kinds of weird shit and
fuck this fucking, and they should have the FBI investigating them. Actually, they already do, but
you know, I'm just having faith in the higher
powers right now but let's see but they are not the ones that you are when you I mean and we tend to some
wear them
You know, but I don't know I I don't know. I'm not I don't know how to explain it
I don't know how to explain it. I see it and I tell it out is how it is
So I don't know how to explain it
I'm just me and just me
And I don't change for anyone.
Okay, I just spilled most of my beer
and so I just ruined my night.
I'm just thinking, what did you spill?
I'm sure it wasn't water.
I spilled it twice.
I spilled it on the table and I spilled it on the floor.
Oh, damn laundry.
I'm just, I still have at least half of it, but fuck.
And now it smells like fucking whatever this hurricane punches
$5
Cash up cult of sight. Um, no, I'm spilling everywhere. Yes. I spill everywhere including on my table. I'm a big
class
but
Red ball game is in here. Do you know what there's a there's a fetish gang that's obsessed with me
And they all have these red balls in their mouths. I think they call themselves the gyms or something like that. Oh, no, the red ball
Okay
The reason why I came on, because I was actually going to bed, I was actually going to bed,
and I was going to turn off my phone, and then I saw a live, oh, because the most times
Right, but I've met I haven't seen you live for a while
Yeah, yeah, I've been off the channel, but I've been on my op on my backup channel and
Distributing from there building that up a little bit, but this is my main speedo channel now, so
Okay
Now, what do you think about the speedo? Do you have a speedo bathing suit? Do I have a speedo bathing suit?
Oh, no. Oh my God. Oh my God. I went to the river the other day. That's what my
nephews found me in, in a beautiful, colorful, I don't know, a colorful bathing suit.
Oh my gosh, we're supposed to be skiing in the river.
Yeah, I didn't do any dipping, but I just had like this one colorful bathing suit.
It's like, I'm old fashioned, you know, just one body and it's very colorful with
And um
So you were a topless or a full one piece. Oh, no, I don't do topless. Oh, come on
I'm you gotta free the free the old ladies that are not old ladies, but free the ladies. I
Don't have lights
What did you do you swim with?
What funny light I don't have like I shouldn't have late we'll have to
Mean the dark
Well, I'm gonna let your way home
Okay, that's your main band thing that could be
You're in trouble big clips that it's you where's your main and you're not thing that is your thing is imposter
They're like, why am I banned?
I don't do, I don't do, oh my god, skinny deep pain, skinny deep pain, oh my god, talking
about skinny deep pain.
Well, that's when you get, you go to like this like a river or lake or a swimming pool
in the middle of the night that's in a closed apartment complex.
Oh my god.
shut up now so I could talk so them them them them ones that are the ones that are
how you call them the air dropping or eyes looking or how they call them how
they call them the ones looking the watchers the watchers yeah whatever they
call them sir they'd love to hear about Jenny so I did a skinny deep in I did
that oh my god many years ago when I did one time I
I did a cycle around the lake of Zurich and on my way back, I stopped at an area and I went skinny dipping.
I went skinny dipping in the lake of Zurich. Wow. Did you get a little fish come bite your toes?
Is it a moonlight? I'm just trying to try to picture this.
I'm just picturing you right now.
It's so funny. You remind me of that. It was so funny. It was such a long time ago. It was my god
It was such a long time ago and I
My 20 when I was in my 20s when it was in my 20s early 30s
I wrote around the lake of Zurich and then I on my way back on my way back home
I thought that's
and skinny deep in the lake of Zurich.
Yeah, it's so amazing.
That sounds like it's a lot of fun.
Can I come visit you?
Sorry?
Can I come visit you in Switzerland?
Oh my god, baby, oh my god, baby, you are welcome.
You are invited.
You're welcome.
I'll see you after the film.
You have to pay your flights, pay your flight, and everything else is on me.
Pay your flight.
Okay, I'm going to pay my flight, I'm going to bring a Toblerone bar, I'm going to bring
Swissmas hot cocoa, and I'm going to bring some Ricola.
That is, you heard of that, you have a Ricola?
Just don't bring, just don't bring Trump, don't bring Trump.
I won't, I won't.
I don't know, he's pretty awful, but he's in Turkey right now, I don't think he can come, but yeah, okay, he'll be there tomorrow, I'm just...
Well, I'm not there right now, I'm actually in the Caribbean, I'm in the Caribbean.
Oh my god, hey.
And you always were the one with James and Joker. I have so much fun
Okay
Yeah, so, um, Mr. Extendope is actually I consider him my streaming father. Okay, because he got me into streaming
Okay, good night. Great blind though. I hope you got a you had a good show and
To your chatters people in the chat I can't always see them and I'm so shut up to your chatters
Hope everybody's having a great time
Good day. So shut up to your people in the chats
And the lookers, as usual, will say hello everybody because they're always looking and looking for things to share and tell and expose.
I know I think it's a good gang. I think I'm being stalked by some crazy internet gang. I don't know. I just have a feeling sometimes, you know.
Well, you know, we have the feelings but always be aware of all feelings and of our consciousness
Always take that to mind what we feel what we feel what we what we what what we react mostly to
be aware and
And take take deep consciousness of that. I
Have a theory. I feel that
Well, first of all, I don't think we attract people into our lives.
I think we attract lessons into our lives sometimes, you know, and these lessons will play out.
We have a lot to learn.
Our biggest, our biggest opponent in life is actually ourself.
Like, we're the one that, probably hard on ourselves.
We're the one that's going to be giving ourselves the most challenges to overcome.
So, even the outside and the inside.
Can I give you a perfect example?
So we all here in the Caribbean island and
We're gonna bury my mom my mom pass
That's okay. That's okay. That's okay. She's lived a beautiful life. She died at 91
That's how I would love to go. That's how I would love to go. That's how everybody
Every one of us that's how we would want to go, right?
How many of us want to go like my mother did?
everybody
everybody so now
We have the whole family coming down together
Everybody's been overseas those who live on the island and those who live overseas they're coming together and
One brother just arrived tonight and I was worried about him
I was totally if you heard in the background he came in asked me question and
right, so I
Was your younger brother or yes?
Definitely yoga brother. Yeah, and so I said, okay
Calm down. They want to celebrate like okay. We can be careful and it's like Jenny
Jenny I don't need you to tell me what to do. I am you're whether you're talking to me
But the funny thing about it is that's the way our mom spoke to us all the time
Who started acting like her a little bit you're saying?
That's the way my mom spoke to us all the time whenever we came and so
Suddenly I felt like I was in the vision of my mom speaking to my brother
you know and so he said he said to me I'm a grown-up now I don't need you to
talk to me that way but I still kept my ground and I said yeah you're young but
I'm older than you but at the same time I need you to be a man and be careful of
what you're doing and not go about driving
under the influence while you're on the islands.
I mean, you live on another island,
but while you've been on the island,
and he said to me, okay, okay.
And it just, so he just came back.
He just came back.
to let me know that he's home safe.
That was nice of him to do that.
He popped into my room to let me know I'm home safe.
But the whole consciousness about it was suddenly,
I feel like I carry a role which is not in me.
It is not like me because they're grown-ups,
they can't do what they do.
I suddenly had this.
Disconsciousness in me that I need to protect that and I felt that my mom my mom was speaking through me telling them
Jenny now. I'm gone
You're the you're the lady-in-charge. You're the head the head queen, right? Yeah. Yeah
Here my boy the men are always kind of like babies and women are kind of always more mature and
kind of like the
Yeah, the mother the mother or the you know the nurturing
I'm just being general here, but I'll say if your family you'll have everybody in your family when they're all alive
even the eldest one is there who is the eldest one above because i've lost a few brothers and
sisters over the years but the last one was elder and now i'm in the middle of the eldest one
and the last one and suddenly i felt this like this energy which is telling me take care of them
They're all with you. They can do things in that world. They can't do in this world.
In the Caribbean, do you notice a spiritual energy? I know there's like very spiritual
roots there and it's a very magical place. What do you think? Is that where she's from?
Or the Caribbean? Mom, mom is from the Caribbean. I'm from the Caribbean, born and raised in the
Caribbean. Yes, yes. Awesome. How about your dad? I mean, where's, where's he from?
Switzerland Iran
All right, would you say he's from or you can just give the general geographical country or
continent even
Is he everything's he from the Caribbean or is he Swiss? I'm just wondering how'd you get into in Switzerland?
You mean with, how do you like, I don't want to share that, I don't want to share that, how I got to Switzerland, but I had a beautiful, I had a beautiful travel until I got to Switzerland, I've lived through many places, I lived through certain Caribbean islands until I got to Switzerland.
And that's where I am based now at the moment.
And it's one of the most beautiful places
that I enjoy coming back to.
And where I am now, where I enjoy coming back to.
So I've got two beautiful, beautiful countries
that I love, that I come back home every year
to second year or three years.
Yeah, so.
Cool.
I mean, it's like, since you're a tribe,
what's your astrological sign?
And do you want me to just sign up for the earth and just sign up for it?
I'm the prairie, yes. I'm the water barrier.
Okay, the prairies are very, they're like the whole world. I mean, that's like the
the consciousness of air. Tell them what the fuck is that. Tell them what the fuck is that.
I'm the water barrier. I'm the saver. I'm the saver. There you go.
Tell them what the fuck is that. The water barrier. It's actually an interesting story.
Like, you know, the god Zeus, are you interested in Greek mythology?
I do, I do actually. I've got my Greek book back home.
When I traveled to Greece, I traveled to Greece and I bought one of these. I've never fully read it.
But the, the, have you, you've met Harry, haven't you?
Yeah, I've been to Greece, too.
I've been to Harry's house because I love Harry.
I'm so attracted to him.
Harry, that's amazing.
Harry's, Harry's.
I saw a picture of him, he was just a skinny weird other guy.
I like his voice, he's done like Joe Rogan kind of.
Oh my God, Harry's like,
Harry sounds like a fucking Italian, like an Italian god.
living in America. That's what he sounds like every time I listen to him. And he's got so much
knowledge and wisdom. Sometimes you go off base. I hope he's listening, Harry. That's compliment to
you. Not everybody agrees with him, but he's got so much knowledge and understanding and wisdom
when he talks about his Greek, Greek mate, this Greek mate. Well, not everything the Greek made.
Right.
They just tell you.
The green people.
Oh, they didn't grease me.
Grease me.
Oh, by the way, I'm sorry.
Yeah, but they didn't grease me to everything, you know.
Grease didn't make everything.
Yeah.
Well, everything is grease.
Grease is turkey.
Grease is this.
Everything is grease.
The time is the place is the motion.
Sorry.
But he's he's all we'd love to miss the Nintendo, but he's knowledgeable to Greek
Anthology and their lifestyle is actually
There are truths to it, right there troops
It's a cradle of civilization modern civilization. I mean Rome came out of Greece. They have the same gods
They just named them up big different things like the planet
Yeah, if you definitely if you go into the background of all of that and the history is there
It's actually it's there for people to see but if you don't travel
How do you know the knowledge if you don't travel? I've been to Greece when I was a 17 or 16 or 17
I went to Greece I was 17
Well, no, I was 15. I went to Greece when I was 15. I stayed with the family first for like a few weeks and then I traveled around
We went to all these monasteries and stuff
But I've always been I've always loved Greek mythology this whole channels based on Greek mythology
But the story of Aquarius real quick is that Zeus
Was you know, he always would cheat on his wife Hera, you know, so he was always out like looking for something like you know
And you know Zeus Zeus was like a he was by I guess and so
You're breaking up you're breaking up. You're so nice darling. Give me now. Give me now. Hello testing. You hear me now
Hello
Well, I want to actually it's on my bucket list. I want to take my son
Because when I went to Greece, my son wasn't born yet.
So that's a trip I want to take my son to, take him to Greece.
When I want to take him to Thailand.
I went to Greece when I was 15.
I went to Thailand when I was 17.
And I went to Spain when I was 14.
So those were my trips.
So do you see why we have this beautiful bond?
Do you see that?
Right.
When things like that happen, they're not coincidences.
I mean, of all the countries of countries, I mean, there's two very, oh, there's a beautiful
connection.
There's a beautiful connection.
Everyone there is friendly to go
And they're like they're like there's a lot of transgender there and Asia has trans
Definitely when you don't even have to go as far as Thailand you just have to go to Amsterdam and you can meet them all there
Right. I went to the Red Light District in Amsterdam
I went to the Red Light District with a couple people that came to like, you know
Took to hook up in the Red Light District, but I know I'm gay, but I walk in the red light because there's no men
Yeah, you're gonna meet the whole universe of trans trans how you call them trans gender or whatever go to
Amsterdam, you've got them. They're all there
I was you know walk out the front door. I mean in America. I mean everyone's going trans here now
I mean, it's like it's just it's just popular. I'm actually I was actually born a biological female and look at me now
When did I go to Thailand?
Yeah, what did I do? What did I do in Thailand? I'm sorry. Someone asked the shot. What did I do in Thailand?
So I started in Bangkok. I was like, you know, it was a homestay kind of thing. So when we sort of Bangkok
Spends the time there and that's pretty wild city, right?
and we were all drinking and stuff because we can drink there when you're in a routine.
And then we went to Chiang Mai, which is in the north, and Chiang Mai is like a really,
everything is pretty, they have this, their currency is called Baht, but it's a very
good exchange rate, so you can buy like a lot of cool stuff. And then we went trekking,
and also we went and did a homestay, we say, I say with a family of farmers,
they're all like five feet tall.
The sun was kind of like more like of the worldly, like he spoke English and Thai,
but the parents were like these little tiny like five foot tall Thai people, they had a farm,
we did community service in the village, all kinds of different tasks and stuff, and they loved us.
We came there, we got this big village well, I mean it's a little village, it was a little tiny
like little farming village, and it was like, it was like living in like 500 years ago because
And then the city and stuff. It was so cool. It was so cool. I was very lucky and we left they felt they all cried
They loved it. We were like giants too because we're all like these big
There's a lot of black girls there because they had a lot of people from New York these girls from New York
There's a couple guys
Thailand in Thailand you have a lot of Americans and you've got a lot of Germans
but i remember the time when i was back there it was a lot of americans
lot of americans because every just about every i mean you know they've got their language
but just about everybody was american it was crazy right it was great yeah because well it's like
i guess a lot of americans will travel at the same time and you know that we're very big tourists and
You know, I was a vegetarian, everything is very spicy,
there's a lot of vegetarian food,
everything is like noodles, like clear noodles,
and like spicy broth and stuff and,
and,
You know
Do you ever follow like the travelers the travelers blogs like there are people that travel to different
Different countries or islands or wherever and they share the foods. I forgot the name but
bloggers or food bloggers like you know
Yeah, I'm full and two of them. I have I don't get their notification very often
But when I do they they both of them have been to Asia and
One guy was recently in Thailand and he went
Through who cares and all of these different places. I'm just trying the food. I'm just and it's not just the foods
But it's just the whole
System of travel travel through the the islands
Right, so sometimes it can be difficult sometimes because they first of all they have the money division and then they have their restrictions
Right, I remember when we got there, they were like,
you don't even talk about the king and queen
because if you say something negative
about the king and queen, you'll hear it.
Oh, day, oh, day, oh, day, oh, day, oh, day, oh, day, oh, day.
That was one thing.
Second of all, we go to Bangkok.
I'm like walking around with these, you know, we're all like walking around the red light district and going we're going to a club
We're like, oh, here's a club in Bangkok
We go on all of a sudden there's like much of the naked people coming out with like sex toys and stuff on this day
Everyone's ran out of the club. I mean, I was like, oh my god. I didn't know it'd be like this
I was I was gonna stay but everyone else ran out. So, um, you know, it is kind of like a lot of sex
It's called Lamb's Smiles and they go Sawadee Ka and they have this really tonal
Yeah
Yeah, you know what they kept saying to me in Greece, they kept telling me, they were like, oh Malacca, that's what they used to say, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they used to do, that's what they
And Philippine, my next, I wanna do Philippine as well.
I have friends in Philippine,
I wanna do Philippine as well.
God give me the grace and blessing.
I wanna go to Filipino.
I wanna do Philippine.
Yeah, that'd be a fun place to go to too.
I know, I have a friend in the Philippines.
Oh my gosh, okay.
So, let me see what I have here.
I have a couple of books, let me see.
What is this one?
Okay.
That's the best title of the album, but this is, I think this one's the grease one.
Let me see if I see something grease.
I travel to Greece 1996 September, okay, so let me see if I find anything interesting
in here.
I was with a group.
Okay.
Here's the toy.
I remember seeing these bathrooms, the European bathrooms are just crazy, right?
Okay, oh, oh the toilet. That's the bathroom in the hotel. It's just like a little
Listen to me. Can I listen to me? I was recently in I was recently in
Turkey I had to use a toilet like that
Turkey you're talking about Turkey or Turkey. Yes, Turkey. Yes, I'm Turkey. Yeah
And then I was, sometimes I do like this day traveling through Switzerland, and where was I, and then I saw the same toilet in Switzerland, I'm like, damn, am I in Turkey, where, where, where, you know, use the toilet on, so, yeah.
I don't like a hole in the floor, but I mean, it's usable, but it's just kind of weird squatting in the shower.
Yeah, it's so different.
putting it on the drain.
You know, this is, hold on,
there's Poseidon right there, Poseidon.
You see that right there, Poseidon?
Yep.
And there's the mask of Agamemnon.
Okay, I see, let's see.
Here's the name of the artifact.
There is Athena, I believe, is that Athena?
No, that is actually, I think Aris,
she's holding an apple.
And actually back then,
I even knew who Aris was,
because I said she's either holding an apple or a grenade.
And then I said,
I'm I was actually pretty funny. I didn't know I said I said, uh, but here we are
Oh, here's pan pan getting feisty with afro value. Well arrows looks on
Right there. Oh my god
Oh my goodness
We look like a un kind of because there's like a lot of different races and see there. I am I'm there
I'm the blonde guy right there. I had my hair bleach at the time
Everybody
What you know what you know what stuff yeah take a pop you know what you're sharing these pictures on albums
Today when you take pictures with the cameras you can send them right down
So I've got I've got like four or five albums with pictures like that when I went to Italy when I went to Rome when I went to
Paris when I went to
Curriculum that's that's the albums that I have at home
So, yeah, I mean, this is all, this is 996, this is 30, this is 30 years old, this is
30 years ago I went, I can't believe it, look at that, oh, look at it, look what I used
to look like, there's me with a cat, we went to this little park and there were all these
cats running around, I had one in my lap and I loved cats even back then, we were playing
with cats.
And then there's me, I was like, I came, see that's me.
Oh my god, you baby look at you. Oh my god
You cute as a jelly bean you cute as a jelly bean
Here so here's the group. I think this is our last day right here
But we made this group so we had of all multicultural people. We're all kind of tired, but
And there's our group, her name is Nikea right there,
she's really cool, her name is Nikea.
Let me see, I think it's all,
wait, I remember it says Kurt Cobain on the graffiti,
I thought that was pretty cool,
cause I was the Kurt Cobain fan, so.
Where is the Kurt Cobain, that's nothing else.
Kurt Cobain, there it is, Kurt Cobain.
meant my bro went to Philippines and he brought me a carton of black bat-sigs.
I hopefully didn't have real bats in them. Your ex-husband's ma, they were strong like cigars.
What your ex-husband is ma? What does that mean? I'm sorry.
But let's, I'll show you, let's see, what else?
Oh, we went to these big monasteries
and there's these big Byzantine,
like Greek Orthodox monasteries and this beautiful art.
You can see the art right there.
It's like there's Jesus and stuff.
I even went to like a baptism, I think there.
Someone's just looking for something.
I love the, I love the Italian history.
I love the Greek history and I love the culture.
I love the culture.
Cool shows and stuff.
See, there's the cool.
And I know we had a very there's the oral post this is seaside village that I stayed at it's hard to see. I'm sorry. There's the group again
I'm exposed to much and you know
This is 30 years ago. You can know no everyone's either dead or here's the baptism
So there's a baptism we went to and it was like crazy. Everyone's crying and screaming
It was just a random baptism, but there's baby and stuff and
Is that cool
Oh look, there he is holding the baby, he's like Lion King, oh, there he is, oh, beautiful.
And oh, okay, so I had a crush on that guy there, very, I did crush on him.
Your problem traveling through the region was the Yugoslav conflicts, go ahead next
door.
So this was 1996.
I don't think there were big conflicts, but there might have been, but uh.
I had a crush on this guy. His name is Dimitris.
He was a friend of... I thought this guy was so cute.
I look at him now and I'm like, he's a nerdy guy.
But this is a guy that I thought was so fine.
I was like, this is my boyfriend right there.
He looks like, he looks like Nintendo but dark hair.
Yes.
I was like, Mr. Nintendo.
Okay, so this is my mother.
I had a mother named Effie.
Her name is Effie.
Yeah.
And that was her mother.
She loved me.
She was like, look, she loved me.
She was like.
Yeah.
She loved me.
My little American she had a fish restaurant by the oh by the beach. They had a little dog. Oh, you want to see my my friend
Christiane Christine at the glass door. Look how pretty they are
I like at age 45 they turn into like old ladies
They're beautiful people there too, you know
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait that picture looks like a cousin of mine
uh-huh a cousin
That picture
She looks like a cousin of mine with that beautiful smile. Oh my goodness that girl
She looks like a cousin of mine. Yep. Wow
Everyone liked me but the brother I had their his name is Yorgos and this is when they say goodbye
So Yorgos hated me, but that was the brother that she loved me. That was her son
So they're very nice little Greek couple or not couple like a mother and son
There's some ruins. I think it is coming to an end
Let's see if there's anything else worth sharing.
I just remembered we do have a...
Yes, darling?
Listen, I might log off with you later,
but I'm going to join the family member
because we will get in together and...
Oh, well, you have a lovely time.
Thank you. I mean, I hope you have a beautiful...
Do it later.
Wait, this is...
The funny thing about it is...
I have the same time zone with you because in Switzerland I'm six six hours ahead of you
So it's always different to connect with you guys, but being on this
Thunder with you. I'm logged on. So I'm gonna join the family member because we all together
Just to prove it look at me how cute I am
Oh my god, you and you haven't changed your hair just got longer. I did
How great guys like how tall I am see see I'm telling me always
You are still the same you your hair just got longer. That's all
I'm a sexy mofo. I can be a speedo and still be confident
i'm that embarrassed listen to me you're sexy mora
Sexy motherfucker.
Think that could be me.
I am gorgeous.
You are so amazing.
I love you.
You're amazing.
Thank you for being my friend.
I love you.
More than you love me.
We're going to have some
Rekhola Kavdrop,
Swiss Miss,
we're going to have some
Toblerone.
We're going to have a real
deal.
I wish I could have had a
Trump mask.
I wish I could have had
a fucking Trump mask.
I had one.
It's the devil.
Oh
Let me see if I can oh no I can't change anything
Wait, wait, let me see if I can let me see if I can change my avatar
You see I can change my average bar the kid Calvin
Change my
Oh my god, I can't oh my Jesus
You just make me broke my bones just thinking about doing that. What the fuck?
I'll break your back
You know you will broke if you want me to do that. I'll break my lower back man. Damn it
Don't make me do that shit. I will make you do it
The aliens are watching you though. Oh my god, they look like the alien
Let the motherfuckers watch the aliens in your morass
Why are her eyes so red? Is she spoke a lot of a lot of weed?
In the Mordas, watch the alien in only Mordas.
That's nail. That looks like Hello Kitty grew up in, you know, kind of, kind of, kind of...
Yeah, sure.
Hey, how about this?
Hey, James Bond.
Yes, nice.
La Dia.
I love you.
The other day we watched the same one, people dressed like horses and moored each other around. It was so great.
I feel like the bass is coming out of me tonight.
Hello, princess.
That was good.
I'm not galling, but here, I'm going to give you a flex in your way out.
Hey, you have a flex.
Twerk, twerk, twerk, twerk, twerk, twerk, twerk, twerk.
Anyways, good luck. Let me tell you something.
I love you so much.
I might connect with you later, but I've got to go connect with the family members
Night care business. I love you. Thanks for coming on the show. You're welcome baby girl, baby boy
Yeah, not yet give me a few years, I have to pay for the implants first
Oh, you see that you see that
Great, I could have said baby boy, but I said baby girl. So what does that mean?
Are you contemplating to go there?
Keep on listening here, buddy!
Okay, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me, leave me
I get the same bullshit with my dreadlocks, man.
When I have to untangle my dreadlocks,
when I, oh, God, you look like Jesus.
Thank you.
You look like Jesus today.
Oh, hold on, I'll take this one down, hold on.
There we go, it says, remove this one.
Okay, so come on.
Come on, Jesus, come up here.
We're up here, I mean, come on, we're short on time.
Here, oh, there it goes, here.
So there's love one another, a new command.
Love you, one love one another.
As I have loved you, you must love one another.
By this, everyone will show that you're my disciples
if you love one another, Jesus.
There you go.
Isn't that, isn't that what he tried to share with everybody, the beauty of life?
Yeah.
And when you yourself walk through life, isn't that what you share with everybody and when
you greet them in harmony and say, good morning, say good morning, madam, and have a great
day and have a blessed day?
Isn't that how you greet people when you walk through life?
Love is the key.
I think love is the key to life.
you know that it's so much so much more beautiful and stronger than hate and more powerful than
hate and it's like you know so much let me tell you something it's not it's there are a lot of
people who are so full of hate and guilt about themselves that they turn against themselves
it's good even if you smoke a joint or whatever you take somebody's oh yeah this is this is me
this is me in my maximum they're making that excuse they're making that excuse oh it's about
alcohol oh it's about smoking but i i'm guessing it could be about um
alcohol or whatever but let me tell you something everybody who has turned against
you on an internet it was meant to be because they targeted themselves to
do that against you because of their guilt that's it
nothing more
their own consciousness of how they feel about life and when you tell them the truth about themselves
if they cannot face it they they they turn against you and they curse you and so it's all about their
own guilt it's all about own guilt it's all about your judge for people hate you about is actually
Perfect. And especially when they see you having such a beautiful life, how does Jenny do it?
How does Jenny do it? She's living every time she comes on our panel. She's happy. She's laughable. She's this.
And we're hearing this about how does Jenny do it? Why she's always happy?
Nobody wants to see a happy person. Why does they're not happy about themselves?
Let me tell you something my beautiful boyfriend twerk your ass to them
And if you want to pull me in your face, pull me in the motherfucking ass face do that for me. I will
Yeah, and if you fucking poop pooping the motherfucking ass do it on your fucking point because you have the right to do that
There you go. There you go
Only one do not because the motherfuckers can never do that
I love it
Anyway, I might join you late if I don't but I'm gonna join the family members because I love you sweetheart. Thank you for coming
Hey, be careful of the what don't don't expose your your private part. I know I'm gonna be careful
I don't have all sec to pop out on the beach. I'm gonna maybe wear another pair of speedos under my
The thing about Alex pull me Alex face
Just give Alex a fucking fat for me if I could do it on your panel right now and fat in his fucking face
I would do that
I told you I told you I told you said oh, I love Alex. I love Alex, but that's what he does
Alex is a motherfucker
He's a motherfucker
Yeah, when I when I say motherfucker and where he's from where's Alex from New York
A
American so when you tell them
Americans how they are misbehaving on fucking public panels. They don't like it
So that are in their fucking speedos on panels. What are these people? What's wrong with these people?
What's wrong with them? Talk about them. They don't like it. They talk about themselves
They want to hear you
Hear them talk about bad about themselves when you talk about themselves bad
They fucking like you the worst of the worst on the fucking planet. Let me tell you
Fuck Americans you motherfuckers
There we go. Hey, there we go. Fuck you micron. Anyway, baby girl
I said it again, so if you gonna, so if you gonna fucking future, I looking forward to it, but I would love you to stay the way you are.
You can be universal. Anyway, I love you so much, you take care.
Enjoy your Paan Hill, enjoy your evening, and I probably, I might log on later if I don't, I'll see you around baby, okay?
Love you, honey, honey pie. Love you.
Thank you for having me on and shout out to Nintendo and shout out to everybody who's been
listening and the motherfucker, Lucas, your motherfuckers. I give you the finger to those
negative. I give you the fucking fingers, your motherfuckers. There you go. I love it.
Thank you.
Thank you, baby. Take care. Chow chow chow
Maha, wow
Watch me on the way out. Look good luck. Good luck and blessings. Love you. There you go. Okay
Bye
I'm
Read not for me not for me not for me, but can you read something for the panel?
Can you do a room for the pun for the people in the chat?
Just randomly pick a pick a car and it's going to be positive. It's going to be positive
Okay, the car I think
The ace of swords is this is the truth. This is receiving or knowing the truth about something something being made clear
something clearing up
This is like the sword of truth, you know, and so no matter what you have like entangling you
You can always cut out of it with this powerful truth. The truth will set you free as they say, right?
Okay, I'll see you I might see you later. If not, I'll see you around. I love you so much my beauty. Take care of yourself
God bless
Okay, okay
Take care
Cha cha
okay guys wow it's not the best night ever and what are people think i'm crazy i mean it's like
what is normal guys so what so what if i like to stream in my speedo i do tarot card readings
vulgar of course yes i'm a tarot card reader i don't like do as many as i i usually ask to be
to do them but i will the truth is the beast weapon fact
Okay, we're talking about the beast. The beast is the world, right? It's like, yeah. Oh, no, sorry. The truth is the best
Best weapon. Yes. It will set you free
Because they are recruiting haters
And look at these scary haters around. He's one of you. Okay. Good night James Bond. Okay, so for
Volga, we go for Volga. I'm gonna
These cards are not traditional tarot cards.
These are called the haters exposed cards,
but I'll pull three of these
and I'll pull three of the regular deck.
So these haters exposed,
first you got a trickster spirit is around, okay?
There's a trickster spirit.
And it says, set in loss of memory,
things end up missing.
And so sometimes when things end up missing,
there's like some, like a little spirit hiding them
or some kind of like, you know.
Something trying to mix you up or maybe mislead you something. They call it the fairies are doing it, right?
But you also have this one that says the person causing the negativity is an earth sign
Okay, and see they have like that one eye out, but it's also like, you know
That's Taurus Virgo or Capricorn. They're the earth signs connect the closest to earth
this has get a
get a
Dreamcatcher to hang over the bed
Maybe that will say save you from some negative energies. It's hard to see that I can barely see that but get a dreamcatcher for your bed, right?
Let's pull two more for out of the stick. Okay, hold on sick. Yeah, we got their social media posts
Memes are directed towards you
Okay, so if you feel like is that okay message for me can be in a good way or bad way
But I think it's maybe the probably like we're trying to do subliminal on you and then the sunflower on the eyes is it says causing
You to miss out on opportunities. Give your eyes open. Don't don't get us don't get distracted by the pretty wall flowers
I got something. Let me get the other deck. This is the bill in the deck
You saw she went live, but uh
She asked that okay, who is she beta went live and she wants me to join the panel
No, she doesn't she doesn't like you always tell me that look who we have we have the Ursula card. There's beta right there
This is, you're not sure about words, wands, cups.
Oh, you're not sure about only,
yeah, that one's a different deck,
but this one is a queen of cups.
And so this has to do with emotions.
And this has to do with maybe that you're,
the feminine side of emotions,
which are very powerful as you're going to get us Ursula,
right?
But women are not like just emotional.
They're the emotional ninjas.
Men are the ones that aren't as good
in control of their emotions.
Women are experts at it,
but they just feel them stronger.
And so,
We also have the Night of Wands.
This is the fastest move.
Is that Night of Wands?
Yeah, this is the fastest moving wand.
It looks like one of the fairy godmothers a little bit.
And it's like, this is like bringing you something really
fast.
There's some fire.
There's some fire power put into it.
It's almost like, bippity boppity boo, a blessing to you.
Because I think it's like, it's from Cinderella.
I don't know.
Maybe not.
I haven't seen all the Disney movies recently.
But it's like, it's somebody that is fast moving.
This is the fastest moving night.
They can either light your fire or maybe burn your house down occasionally.
You just have to like take away the masses from them.
We also have this one, the Hierophant.
Higher guidance.
There's a higher, see those glasses that they're wearing?
It's like a higher power pulling you up and some, or something ceremonial maybe.
Okay.
So I hope that made sense for you.
I'm pulling two more out of the spectrum, let me see.
For Volga, what's this?
Ten of coins this one is
Generational wealth, you know a castle or something passed down to you some there's like a gate. There's the arch over it
There's up. This is really good. This is the wealthiest card everyone's a ten of ten of coins because that's happened money, right?
And I said one or two months. Okay. We also have the three of coins
This is like investing with somebody using it using it wisely
Working with other people other people want to work with you or something like that. You're gonna make money together
I'll put one more
And that's another coin card. So there's something good with money coming for you and we have a tower
I can't end it on this tower though. Okay, so there's gonna be a big shake up something gonna shake up something and change
Things around it. Maybe didn't expect but the I think towers usually are just clearing clearing the way for something
And in this case, it would be for more options for you.
There's gonna be a lot of options after that big thing.
There's gonna be a lot more things open to you
than are right now, and you have to pick the one you want.
Don't get distracted or confused by them,
pick the one you want.
Finally, God, 10 of cups.
This is, wow, this is crazy.
This is the 10 of cups is like the happiness.
You have the two best 10s,
the 10 of cups and the 10 of pentacles.
These are happiness, generational wealth,
fulfillment, all kinds of good shit.
So, yeah, I don't think Bita wants me to join her fam because Bita's
She says horrible things. She said that she could stay away from this disgusting monster or whatever should be
I'm not a disgusting monster. I mean that they had this AM
I don't know who you know who AM is. I just have to use her initials right now for legal purposes, but AM said
Oh, I need to apologize to Bita. To Bita. Well, I was you know, I've only made a thousand
Horrible, you know, videos doxing her and all this stuff, but well, Bita, I'm sorry. I see how psyched he treated you. He made you cry
Beat it, fuck it, make me cry, okay?
He doesn't cry.
Beat it, beat it, has water drip out of her eyes
when she gets to any white claws, okay?
Anyway, let's not get into it.
So how are we doing?
Okay, well, I guess everyone's leaving,
so I guess I'm gonna wrap it up.
I know, I'm just, I'm feeling so stupid
just sitting here alone at my Speedos after 10 p.m.,
so I can't get alcohol anymore.
So, this is fair and glow when we first fell in love.
Do I look that bad?
I mean, yeah, that's when I started looking
a little bit drunk.
Look how drunk we are.
You're welcome, Volga, anytime.
And I hope you liked it, okay?
So, maybe I'll end.
I'll see how many people stay.
Everyone's probably gonna run to BTS,
but I'm not allowed in her chat nor on her panel,
but let's do what happens.
Maybe I'll just go on my Speedo and surprise everybody.
But don't tell her, I won't do it.
Someone's gonna say,
I was playing on Jordan's Speedo,
and then she won't laugh this time.
Last year on this time, I made her laugh her butt off trust me. Hi, Rudy. Okay. Let's enjoy it. Bye. Let's see you later
Rudy
Crackle you can actually watch me